<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="changelog_full_title">Changelog</string>
    <string name="changelog_title">What\'s New</string>
    <string name="changelog_show_full">more&#8230;</string>

    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_cat_title">Reverse Engineering</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_explain_title">Oh, Hi there!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_explain_summary">As you may have noticed the recent GNL update broke all functionality of XGELS. This is due to the complete obfuscation of the GNL apk. To make XGELS work again I had to reverse engineer each feature of XGELS and basically had to go through all my and even the GNL source code again. Luckily I was able to restore 99% of the features!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_conclusion_title">What does that mean?</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_conclusion_summary">It is assumed that Google obfuscates GNL with every major release (3.X) again, meaning that XGELS will break most likely. But this time I\'m prepared and I\'m certain I can restore the same functionality within a few hours!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_what_to_do_title">What can I do?</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_what_to_do_summary">If you don\'t want GNL/Google Search to break XGELS you can go to the Google Play Store and disable automatic updates. GNL/Google Search uses staged rollouts, which means in some cases XGELS gets updated before you even receive the official GNL/Google Search update. You can click here to open the Play Store and disable the automatic update right now!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_bugs_title">Bugs</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_bugs_summary">Due to the reverse engineering there might still be a few bugs here and there. Please be a little bit more forgiving, don\'t ruin my Play Store rating with bug reports. Use the \"Send bug report\" function in the settings menu. Thank you!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_support_cat">I need your support!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_support_title">Donate to me!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_support_summary">It\'s an incredible amount of work for me to maintain XGELS and give good support to you guys. If you feel like donating to me, click here! (!This won\'t unlock Premium!)</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_rate_title">Rate XGELS!</string>
    <string name="pref_reverseengineering_rate_summary">Show your support and leave me a rating on Google Play. A good reputation will motivate others to try XGELS, too. Click here to rate XGELS on Google Play!</string>
</resources>